export default data = [
  {
      question: "My sister wants to buy a car ______ she doesn’t have enough money",
      options: ["because","but","if","or"],
      correct_option: "but"
  },
  {
      question: "Jim always forgets my birthday. He has asked me many times and still can’t ______ it",
      options: ["answer","celebrate","remember","understand"],
      correct_option: "remember"
  },
  {
      question: "The little girl was ______ by a truck on her way home and was badly hurt",
      options: ["hit","led","lost","paid"],
      correct_option: "hit"
  },
  {
      question: "Excuse me. I really need to go now. My kids ______ for me at school",
      options: ["are waiting","were waiting","wait","waited"],
      correct_option: "are waiting"
  },
  {
      question: "Amy’s father is very sick. The doctors can do nothing for him, so Amy went to the temple to for ______ him",
      options: ["care","count","look","pray"],
      correct_option: "pray"
  },
  {
      question: "I’m glad that my school has students wear ______. I don’t have to worry about what clothes to wear to school",
      options: ["belts","caps","gloves","uniforms"],
      correct_option: "uniforms"
  },
  {
      question: "We are surprised that Sally and Ray decided to get married. No one knows ______. They often fight with each other and are unhappy together",
      options: ["why","where","when","how"],
      correct_option: "why"
  },
  {
      question: "I don’t think Katie will read any one of the books you’ve picked out for her: ______ look(s) very boring",
      options: ["it","one","some","they"],
      correct_option: "they"
  },
  {
      question: "Jenny’s bag is very heavy because ______ filled with toy cars",
      options: ["it is","they are","there is","there are"],
      correct_option: "it is"
  },
  {
      question: "______ a map with you when you go to a place for the first time",
      options: ["Have taken","Take","Taking","To take"],
      correct_option: "Take"
  },
  {
      question: "The weather ______ rainy and cloudy in the last few days. I hope the sun will come out soon",
      options: ["has been","had been","will be","would be"],
      correct_option: "has been"
  },
  {
      question: "All the excuses Nick made ______ a lot about how much he hates to do the job",
      options: ["say","saying","which say","to say"],
      correct_option: "say"
  },
  {
      question: "Sabine walks so ______ in the apartment that sometimes you don’t even know she’s just passed by. You wonder if her feet ever touch the floor",
      options: ["freely","lightly","shyly","slowly"],
      correct_option: "slowly"
  },
  {
      question: "In the past, people thought it was a ______ idea to send e-mails and read news online, but now it is part of our everyday life",
      options: ["simple","popular","good","fresh"],
      correct_option: "popular"
  },
]
